{"test_questions": [[{"question": "The output will be a LOW for any case when one or more inputs are zero in a(n):", "opta": "OR gate", "optb": "NOT gate", "optc": "AND gate", "optd": "NAND gate", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If a signal passing through a gate is inhibited by sending a low into one of the inputs, and the output is HIGH, the gate is a(n):", "opta": "AND", "optb": "NAND", "optc": "NOR", "optd": "OR", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A single transistor can be used to build which of the following digital logic gates?", "opta": "AND gates", "optb": "OR gates", "optc": "NOT gates", "optd": "NAND gates", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The logic gate that will have HIGH or \"1\" at its output when any one of its inputs is HIGH is a(n):", "opta": "OR gate", "optb": "AND gate", "optc": "NOR gate", "optd": "NOT gate", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many NAND circuits are contained in a 7400  NAND IC?", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "4", "optd": "8", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Exclusive-OR (XOR) logic gates can be constructed from what other logic gates?", "opta": "OR gates only", "optb": "AND gates and NOT gates", "optc": "AND gates, OR gates, and NOT gates", "optd": "OR gates and NOT gates", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many truth table entries are necessary for a four-input circuit?", "opta": "4", "optb": "8", "optc": "12", "optd": "16", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A NAND gate has:", "opta": "LOW inputs and a LOW output", "optb": "HIGH inputs and a HIGH output", "optc": "LOW inputs and a HIGH output", "optd": "None of the these", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The basic logic gate whose output is the complement of the input is the:", "opta": "OR gate", "optb": "AND gate", "optc": "INVERTER gate", "optd": "comparator", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What input values will cause an AND logic gate to produce a HIGH output?", "opta": "At least one input is HIGH.", "optb": "At least one input is LOW.", "optc": "All inputs are HIGH.", "optd": "All inputs are LOW.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}